Guide to the Eric Moe Collection, 1976- UA.90.F96
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- She Goes Her Spacious Way, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Note: Based on poem by Emily Dickinson
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 5 pages., 3.
- Drummmmmz, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score., 2.
- Let Me Tell U About R Specials, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Instrumentation: [Flute; Electroacoustic Sound.]
  Commissioned by: Patti Monson
  Dedication: For Patti Monson
  Note: Alternate title on some drafts is "Service Economy."
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts. Undated., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 14 pages. 2 copies., 4.
- Market Forces, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Soprano Saxophone, Alto Saxophone, Tenor Saxophone, Baritone Saxophone.
  Commission: [commissioned by the New York Saxophone Quartet]
  At end: "3/20/05 12:40 pm"
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 1.
  - Computer-generated holograph with corrections in blue marker. 18 pages., 2.
  - Computer generated holograph of "honey is sweeter than cash.", 1.
  - Computer-generated holograph of "the prodigal princess" / "the sad story of the prodigal princess", 1.
  - Computer-generated holograph of "bottom line.", 1.
  - Computer-generated holograph of "Market Forces" with corrections in pencil., 1.
- & A Warm Hello From the Alien Ant Farm, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: There are multiple versions.
  Notes: Based on text by Bill Kushner. Four movements: Rain; [& A Warm Hello From the Alient Ant Farm]; Sad Story; [Big Joe]. Drafts of "& A Warm Hello..." are titled "Ant!" Drafts of "Big Joe" are titled "Big Joe Cloud."
  At end: [Big Joe]: "March 20, 2005 Pittsburgh, PA"
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. "Ant!" 4 leaves., 1.
  - Autograph manuscript and computer-generated holograph pages. "Rain.", 1. (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Superhero, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Flute, Clarinet, Violin, Cello, Percussion, Piano.
  Commission: [Commissioned by the New York New Music Ensemble]
  Note: Three movements: I. Learning to fly; II. Early loss; 3. Rescuing the planet in distress; 4. Existential crisis - what's it all for.
  - Computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages with multiple instrumentations (piano, piano/violin, piano/percussion, piano/bass clarinet, etc.)., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations.47 pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 47 pages., 3.
- I Have Only One Itching Desire, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Dedication: to Paul Vallancourt
  Commissioned by: Carson McCullers Center for Writers and Musicians
  At end: "Pittsburgh 1/15/2006"
  - Percussion score. Computer-generated drafts. Undated., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 23 pages., 2.
- Flex Time, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Instrumentation: Violin
  Commissioned by: [Curtis Macomber]
  Note: Drafts have two different titles: Jitterbug and Flex Time. Flex Time is the final title.
  - Violin score. Autograph and computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages., 1.
- All Sensation is Already Memory, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Instrumentation: Flute and piano.
  Notes: [Written for Tara O'Connor and Margaret Kampmeier.] Two movements: I. The Ungraspable Advance of the Past; II. Devouring the Future.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 20 pages., 2.
- Heavenly Labials, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Soprano, Mezzo-Soprano, Cello.
  Commissioned by: Phoenix Commissions for Seraphim
  At end: "8/16/07 Virginia Center for the Creative Arts"
  Note: Based on text by Wallace Stevens. Three movements: I. The Plot against the Giant; II. Worms at Heaven's Gate; III. Nomad Exquisite.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 6 leaves., 1.
  - Stevens text. 2 pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts. Partial drafts of movements II and III., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages. Dates range from 8/17 to 8/20., 4.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Dated 8/20., 5.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 15 pages, including title page, performance notes and text of poems., 6.
- Gong Tormented, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Percussion [2 Chau gongs, Chinese opera gong, suspended cymbal].
  Commissioned by: [Dominic Donato].
  At end: "Pittsburgh, 5/10/2007"
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts. Dated and undated., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 7 pages, including title page/performance notes., 3.
- Grand Prismatic for Clarinet in Bb and Piano, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Clarinet, Piano.
  Commissioned by: Jean Kopperud.
  At end: 8/4/2007 / Montana Artists Refuge / Basin, MT"
  Note: Performed by Jean Kopperud and Stephen Gosling, Merkin Concert Hall, New York, NY, 2/23/09.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 4 leaves., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations. 21 pages, including title page and performance notes., 1.
- Mud Wrestling at the O.K. Corral, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Cello, Piano.
  Commissioned by: David Russell.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 4 leaves., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations. 18 pages., 2.
  - Computer-generated score. Stapled. 20 pages, including title page and performance notes. One copy has "old" written in upper-right corner of cover page. 2 copies., 3.
- Frozen Rain, Summer Dreams, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Notes: Drafts have two different titles: "Idyll" and "Frozen Rain, Summer Dreams." Later copies list "Frozen Rain, Summer Dreams" as title. Written for the Van Cliburn Foundation American Composers International Competition, Rob Frankenberry, Bellefield Auditorium, [Pittsburgh, PA], 11/17/08.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 2 leaves., 1.
  - Piano score. Computer-generated sketches., 2.
  - Piano score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 3.
- Untitled Work, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Instrumentation: Piano and Drum Set..
  - Full score. Computer-generated sketches., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations. Pages 1-13., 1.
- Idyll, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Notes: [Created as a multimedia piece to accompany video by Suzie Silver and Hilary Harp. "AV Lodge Presents: Fruit Machine 2008 Pittsburgh Biennial," Pittsburgh Center for the Arts, 6/18/08.]
  - Piano score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 1.
  - Piano score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations.4 pages., 2.
  - Piano score. Computer-generated score. 4 pages., 1.
- Kick & Ride - Concerto for Drum Set & Orchestra, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: 2 Flutes (1 piccolo), 2 Oboes (1 English Horn), 2 Clarinets in B-flat (1 Bass Clarinet), 2 Bassoons, 2 Horns in F, 2 Trumpets in B-flat, Tenor Trombone, Drum Set (ride, hi-hat, and crash cymbals; 3 tomtoms, snare drum; pedal bass drum), Marimba, Piano, Strings.
  Commission: Commissioned by the Barlow endowment for Music Composition at Brigham Young University. At end: "8/19/08 / Basin, MT"
  Notes: Two movements: I. The Cracked Tune That Chronos Sings; II. Slipstream. [Performed by Boston Modern Orchestra Project, Robert Schultz Percussion, Gil Rose, conductor, at Jordan Hall, Boston, MA, 5/22/09.]
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 2 leaves., 1.
  - Piano and Drum Set score. Computer-generated sketches., 2.
  - Piano and Drum Set score. Computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages. Movement I., 1.
  - Piano and Drum Set score. Computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages. Movement II., 1.
  - Drum Set part. Computer-generated score. 21 pages, missing pages 16-17., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pen notations. 175 pages., 1. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pen notations. 173 pages., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft.173 pages, double-sided printing. Note in upper-right corner of title page: "draft.", 1. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 173 pages., 1.
- The Crowds Cheered as Gloom Galloped Away, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Commissioned by: [Volti.]
  Notes: [Performed by Volti, St. Mark's, Berkely, CA, 2/27/09, and St. Gregory's, San Francisco, CA, 2/28/09.] Includes text by Matthea Harvey.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 1.
  - Text with pencil notes., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages. Pencil notations., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score.16 pages., 4.
- Dead Cat Bounce, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Bass Clarinet, Violin, Viola, Cello, Piano.
  Commissioned by: [counter)induction.]
  Note: Drafts have two different titles: "Based on a True Story" and "Dead Cat Bounce." Later drafts list "Dead Cat Bounce" as title. [Performed Merkin Concert Hall, New York, NY, 6/15/09.]
  - Autograph manuscript sketches.10 leaves., 1.
  - Computer-generated sketches. 2 leaves., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts. Assorted pages., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 4.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts. Pencil notations. Dated on title page: 3/20 (22 pages), 3/24 (30 pages), and 4/5 (29 pages)., 5.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations.41 pages., 6.
- Frozen Hours Melt Melodiously into the Past, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Flute, Clarinet in B-flat, Bass Clarinet, Violin, Viola, 'Cello, Piano.
  Commissioned by: The Jebediah Foundation New Music Commissions.
  Dedicated to: The Firebird Ensemble.
  At end: VCCA 6/14/2009
  Note: Original title (?): Frozen Hours Melt into the Past. Performance and program notes before the score.
  - Full score. Computer-generated. 39 pages., 1.
  - Parts. Computer-generated. Printed back-to-back. Flute, Violin, Viola, Cello., 2.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 3.
    a. Dated 6/14. 48 pages. b. Dated 6/9. pp. 19-37. c. Dated 6/10. pp. 2-37. d. Dated 6/11. pp. 28-32. e. Dated 6/12. pp. 19-27. f. Dated 6/12B: pp. 21-38.
- Jozaphine Dream, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Soprano, Clarinet in B-flat/Bass Clarinet, Piano/Keyboard Sampler.
  At end: Ucross, WY, 8/21/2009.
  Note: Text by Denise Duhamel. Performance notes and texts on preliminary pages. Original title: Fame is no plant that grows on mortal soil. Texts and correspondence with the poet included. 6 movements. I. If you like maraschino cherries, you'll love my nipples. II. It isn't easy being the daughter of Captain America. III. Award acceptance speech. IV. I'm a goddess, not an octopus. V. Interview. VI. It hasn't been easy.
  - Computer-generated score. [4], 42 pages., 1.
  - Computer-generated score. 48 pages., 2.
  - Computer-generated score. 42 pages. Lacks preliminary pages. Corrections in pencil., 3.
  - Computer-generated score. 42 pages. Hole-punched., 4.
  - Computer-generated score. 43 pages. Lacks title page., 5.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 6.
    a. Dated 7/4. pp. 1-4. No text underlay. b. Dated 7/8. pp. 1-6. No text underlay; corrections/additions in pencil. c. Dated 7/9. pp. 7-8. No text underlay; corrections/additions in pencil. d. Dated 7/28. pp. 1-9. Text underlay; corrections/additions in pencil. e. Dated 8/6. pp. 12-18. No text underlay; corrections/additions in pencil. f. Undated. pp. 10-17. g. Undated. pp. 22-28. h. Dated 8/13. pp. 1-12. Corrections in pencil. i. Dated 8/13B. pp. 10-13. Some text added in pencil above staff. j. Dated 8/14. pp. 14-20. No text underlay; corrections/additions in pencil. k. Dated 8/15. pp. 7-9. l. Dated 8/15B. pp. 8-10. m. Dated 8/21. pp. 21-23. n. Dated 9/16. pp. 1-16. Corrections in blue and black pencil. o. Dated 9/25. pp. 1-40. Corrections in blue and black pencil. p. Dated 10/8. 42 pages. Includes texts and performance notes. "For Haleh Abghari" before notes. q. Undated. 39 pages. Corrections in pencil.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. [11] bifolios., 7.
- Lavished Sunlight, Frozen Hours, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Instrumentation: Soprano, Cello, Piano
  At end: Pittsburgh, 5/7/2009
  Note: Texts by Richard Wilbur.
  - Computer-generated score. 27 pages (439 measures), 1.
  - Computer-generated score. 27 pages (436 measures), 2.
  - Sketches., 3.
    a. Manuscript. 4 bifolios. b. Texts. [2] leaves. Typewritten. Composer's sketching out and analysis of texts. Title on leaf [1]: Two songs in a stanza of Beddoes'. Title on leaf [2]: Anterooms.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 4.
    a. Undated. pp. 1-3, 10, 15-20, 25-27 (439 measures) b. Undated. pp. 1-27 (418 measures) c. Dated 4/13. p. [1]. d. Dated 4/16: pp. 2-4. e. Dated 4/17. p. 4. f. Dated 4/17B. pp. 4-6. g. Dated 4/18. pp. 3-7. h. Dated 4/20. pp. 9-10. i. Dated 4/21. pp. 8-10. j. Dated 4/22. pp. 9-10. k. Dated 4/23. pp. 10-11. l. Dated 4/24. pp. 9-12. m. Dated 4/28. pp. 1-12, 14. n. Dated 4/29. pp. 9-12. o. Dated 4/28B. pp. 12-13. p. Dated 4/30. pp. 12-14. q. Dated 5/1. pp. 14-15. r. Dated 5/1B. pp. 14-15. s. Dated 5/1C. pp. 14-15. t. Dated 5/2. pp. 14-20. u. Dated 5/3. pp. 16-19. v. Dated 5/4. pp. 19-20. w. Dated 5/5. pp. 20-22. x. Dated 5/5B. pp. 21-23. y. Dated 5/6. pp. 21-26. z. Dated 5/6B. p. 24. aa. Dated 5/7. p. 1 bb. Dated 5/7B. pp. 22-27.
- Multiple Untitled Pieces, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Bass Clarinet, DX7II.
  Note: These folders contains more than one untitled sketch or draft. Because they are untitled and undated, and because they are sketches (and therefore difficult to clearly link with each other or finished pieces), they are grouped together.
  - Photocopies of autograph manuscript score. Includes pencil corrections, 4 pages., 1.
  - Computer printout of DX7 II Voices. Includes pencil notes. 4 pages., 2.
  - Autograph manuscript draft. 50 leaves (13 blank). In the same packet are photocopies of autograph manuscript drafts, 7 pages., 3.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 44 leaves (13 blank). Found between "Kicking and Screaming" and "Sad Steps and Fancy Footwork.", 1. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 92 leaves (29 blank). In the same packet is a computer generated holograph (1 page)., 2.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 14 leaves (1 blank). Found in same packet, a computer generated holograph with pencil corrections (2 pages). Found between "Blue Air" and "Fled is that Music.", 1. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 36 leaves (3 blank). Found between "Blue Air" and "The Shocked Music of Pearls.", 2.
- Articles, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Note: This folder contains drafts of articles. Publication dates or status is not known.
  - Mozart's K.515, First Movement: A General Discussion. Typewritten (13 pages) and photocopies (10 pages)., 1.
  - Schonberg's "Easy Life": The First Movement of the Piano Concerto. Typewritten (12 pages) and photocopies (3 pages)., 2.
- Recording Notes, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Note: This folder contains recordings notes dated 3/2/95 for a project listed only as "Hayes Biggs."
  - Notes on sound recordings. Photocopy and pencil notes. 11 pages., 1.
- Morning's Minion, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Computer generated drafts. Pen and pencil corrections. 27 pages.., 1.
- Mouth Music, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Instrumentation: Not indicated.
  - Notes and charts written on back of "Kicking and Screaming" scores. 46 pages (17 in pencil, 21 by computer, 8 blank)., 1.
- Sorrow Laughs, Joy Weeps, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Pen and pencil corrections. 9 pages., 1.
- Trying So Hard to Keep It Together, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Instrumentation: E-flat Alto Saxophone, B-flat Tenor Saxophone, E-flat Baritone Sax.
  - Autograph Manuscript sketches. 4 leaves (1 blank), 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft with pencil corrections. 17 pages. Note at top of draft: "10/28.", 2.
  - Notes on sound recording. 1 page., 3.
- Urban Waltzes, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: not listed.
  Note: Title handwritten on first page.
  - Computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages., 1.
- Play Melancholy, Baby, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Flute, piano.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 4 leaves., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated dated revised pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Dated 8/22. 15 pages. 2 copies., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Undated. 15 pages., 4.
- What Time? / Flex Time / Toss & Turn / Power Struggle, undated; 1. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Notes: Four different titles listed on various drafts. No clean final copy without revisions.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated drafts and dated revised pages., 2.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Alto flute.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 1.
  - Autograph manuscript draft. "Alto fl" notated in upper left-hand corner. Partial score., 2.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Instrumentation: English horn, Bass clarinet, Viola, Piano.
  - Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. Pages 1-14., 1.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Piano score. Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations. Pages 1-6., 1.
  - Piano score. Computer-generated draft. 7 pages., 2.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft. Handwritten notation on one page: "II. Alla Breve.", 1.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  Instrumentation: Not designated. Possibly piano.
  - Computer-generated draft. Pencil notations. Pages 3-5, multiple versions of each page., 1.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Instrumentation: Piccolo, Clarinet, Violin, Cello, Percussion, Piano.
  - Computer-generated draft. Pen and pencil notations. Pages 39-47., 1.
- Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Instrumentation: Violin 1, Violin 2, Viola, Piano
  - Full score. Computer-generated draft and dated revised pages., 1.
- Wordless Air, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Instrumentation: Soprano, Flute, Clarinet in B-flat, Violin, Viola, Cello, Piano
  At end: 5/27/2009.
  Note: No text. Title of the work varies on the different versions.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 1.
    a. Undated. pp. 1-3, 5-35. Additions and corrections in pencil. b. Undated. p. 1. Title: Cantando. c. Dated 5/17. pp. 1-2. Title: Canto. d. Dated 5/18. pp. 2-3. Pencil additions. e. Dated 5/26. pp. 1-4. f. Dated 5/27. pp. 1-4. Additions and corrections in pencil. On caption (in pencil): At a loss for words. The words are lost, but the tune remains. g. Dated 6/2. pp. 1-2. Pencil corrections. Title: The words are lost, but the tune remains. h. Dated 6/2B. pp. 1-4. Additions and corrections in pencil. Title on caption (in pencil): On the verge of speech. i. Dated 6/3. pp. 2-3, 11-13, 15. Additions and corrections in pencil. j. Dated 6/6. pp. 3-5. Additions and corrections in pencil. k. Dated 6/6B. pp. 4-11. Additions and corrections in pencil. l. Dated 6/8. pp. 24-30. Additions and corrections in pencil. m. Dated 6/8B. pp. 25-29. Additions and corrections in pencil.
- Hot Keys, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Instrumentation. Piano.
  Dedication: For Wayne Peterson.
  At end: VCCA (Virginia Center for the Creative Arts) and Montana Artists Refuge, May-June 2010.
  - Sketches., 1.
    a. Manuscript. [21] leaves. b. Manuscript. [6] leaves. Photocopy. Water-stained.
  - Scores., 2.
    a. Computer-generated. 19 pages. b. Computer-generated draft. 19 pages.
- Spirit Mountain, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  Instrumentation. Flute, Oboe, Bassoon, Percussion, Piano.
  Dedication: "J. Karla Lemon in memoriam"—Caption.
  Note: Supported by the Pew Center for Arts & Heritage through the Philadelphia Music Project.
  - Computer-generated score. 30 pages. "C-score.", 1.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 2.
    a. Undated. [2] leaves. Piano reduction. b. Dated 7/9. pp. 1-3. c. Dated 7/10. p. 4. d. Dated 7/13. p. [1]. e. Dated 7/18. pp. 2-7. f. Dated 8/3B. pp. 2-4. Piano reduction. g. Dated 8/9. pp. 2-3. Piano reduction. h. Dated 8/9. pp. 1-8. Full score. i. Dated 8/10. pp. 1-14. Full score. j. Dated 8/17. [1] leaf k. Dated 8/30. pp. 1-18, 22-24. Corrections in pencil and pink ink. Printed in green ink. "J.K.L. in memoriam"—Caption. l. Dated 9/6. pp. 18-21. Corrections in pencil. m. Dated 9/9. pp. 1-29. Corrections in pencil and blue ink.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. [8] leaves., 3.
- Strenuous Pleasures, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Flute, Clarinet in B-flat, Violin, Cello, Drumset, Marimba, Piano.
  Dedication: For Paul Lanksy.
  Commission: Mandel Foundation and the 2010 Utah Arts Festival.
  - Full score. Computer-generated. 32 pages. Printed double-sided., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated. 75 pages. Additions and corrections in pencil., 2.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. [12] leaves., 3.
  - Drafts., 4.
    a. Computer-generated. Score format. 1. Undated. p. 1. 2. Undated. pp.1-2. 3. Undated. pp.1-5. 4. Undated. pp. 31-35.
    b. Computer-generated. Piano reduction. 1. Undated. [1] leaf. 2. Undated. p. 1. 3. Undated. p. 1. 4. Undated. pp. 1-5 5. Undated. pp. 1-10. 6. Undated. pp. 9-11. 7. Undated. pp. 8-12. 8. Undated. pp. 8, 10-16 (several versions of pp. 15-16). 9. Dated 2/13. pp. 1-12. 10. Dated 2/14. pp. 12-13. 11. Dated 2/15. pp. 13-14. 12. Dated 2/15C. pp. 14-15. 13. Dated 2/18. pp. 14-15. 14. Dated 2/20. pp. 15-17. 15. Dated 2/21. pp. 16-17. 16. Dated 2/23. pp. 6-20. 17. Dated 2/25. pp. 17-20. 18. Dated 2/26. pp. 18-20. 19. Dated 2/27. p. 10. 20. Dated 3/2. pp. 20-21. 21. Dated 3/5. pp. 19-24. 22. Dated 3/6. pp. 19, 23-24. 23. Dated 3/7. pp. 17-24. 24. Dated 3/8. pp. 21-24. 25. Dated 3/10. pp. 16-17. 26. Dated 3/12. p. 24. 27. Dated 3/13. pp. 17-18, 24. 28. Dated 3/14B. pp. 18-19.
    c. Computer-generated. Full score. 1. Undated. pp. 1-24 (complete?). 2. Undated. pp. 1-67 (incomplete). Various titles in pencil on caption: I hear time's winged chariot; And hear our pleasures; Strenuous pleasures. 3. Dated 3/14. pp. 1-8. 4. Dated 3/19. pp. 42-47. 5. Dated 3/23. pp. 65-68, 72-73 (several versions of pp. 65-67). 6. Dated 3/24. pp. 65-77. 7. Dated 4/5. pp. 65-77.
    d. Handwritten notes on the piece. [2] pages.
- Danger: Giant Frogs, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Percussion (4 players)
  Dedication: To the memory of Serge and Natalie Koussevitsky. For Talujon.
  Note: Completed at Copland House, Cortland manor, NY as a recipient of the Aaron Copland Award.
  - Working documents for instrumentation/rhythms. [7] pages., 1.
  - Computer-generated full scores., 2.
    a. Dated 5/15. 50 pages. Corrections in pencil and red ink. b. Dated 5/24. 52 pages. Includes performance notes.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 3.
    a. Dated 5/9. 51 pages. b. Dated 5/9. 50 pages (incomplete). c. Undated. 21 pages. d. Undated. pp. 34-44.
- I Want a Boyfriend with Antlers, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Voice, Piano.
  Dedication: For Tom Cipullo.
  Note: Text by Denise Duhamel.
  - Computer-generated score. 8 pages. Printed on the verso of some pages of the score are drafts dated 2/2/11., 1.
  - Texts. Typewritten. [1] leaf. Title: Ten qualities as a Cosmo girl I really want in my man. Dedication: For Jean Valentine, after seeing Bambi., 2.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. [2] bifolios., 3.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated score., 4.